RAINISA SOFHIA

+62 853-8666-4620



rainisasofhia@gmail.com



Indonesia



Jr. Frontend Developer

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>Github</u> <u>Website</u> <u>Instagram</u>

SUMMARY

Junior frontend developer enthusiast in developing user interfaces for web applications. Recently finished my study at Alterra Academy for Frontend Engineer program where I'd worked on some personal and group projects like database movie app, e-commerce app, and booking app. Skilled in HTML ,CSS, Javascript, ReactJS and TailwindCSS. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team. Willing to relocate within Indonesia.

SKILLS

- English
- SQL
- HTML & CSS
- ExpressJS
- ReactJS
- Cit
- VueJS
- · Problem solving
- Javascript
- Communication skills
- Tailwindcss
- Teamwork
- Bootstrap

EDUCATION

Alterra Academy

Immersive Program, Frontend Engineering September 2020 – December 2020

Mulawarman University

Bachelor of Education, English Education September 2012 – December 2020

CERTIFICATIONS

- Membangun Website dengan Wordpress
 & HTML bagi Pengembang Internet
 (Issued by <u>International Design School</u>)
- Menjadi Javascript Engineer menggunakan Javascript dan Node.js bagi Developer IT dan Programmer Web (Issued by Course-Net)

PROJECTS

Let'sWatch

Let's Watch is an online database of information related to movies – including plot summaries, rating, genres and other related information. Users can browse and find all information about the movie and add them to their favorite or remove them from their favorite. This project used TMDB API, ReactJS, Tailwind css and was deployed using Vercel. See the source on Github.

Bengcall

Bengcall app wehere users can book a vehicle service based on their vehicles & update or delete their account. This app also provide some features for admins to take care service data. Collaborated with Backend and Quality engineer and built using ReactJS, Tailwind css, DaisyUI and deployed on Vercel. See the source on Github.

ALTAFASHION

E-commerce app where users can browse and discover many products, add them to their carts and buy them. Users can also sell their own product. Collaborated with Backend and developed using ViteJS, Tailwind css and was deployed on Vercel. See the source on Github.

Web Portfolio

Simple website created as a web portofolio. This project was developed using ReactJS, Tailwind css and was deployed on Vercel. See the source on <u>Github</u>.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Teaching Staff

UPT. Bahasa Mulawarman University | 2019 - Present

English Tutor

Freelance | 2015 - Present

Teaching Assistant

KUMON | 2017 - Present